

GEORGE BANLAKI

INFO



Address

26 Thorn Apartments, 5 Geoff Cade Way, E34GJ



Phone

+44 7469 201579



Email

george.banlaki@gmail.com

SKILLS

General IT skills

(Word, Excel, Outlook, Opera)

HTML / CSS

Javascript / jQuery

PHP

MySQL

Adobe Photoshop

Problem solving skills

Communication skills

Service Orientation

Time Management

OBJECTIVE

A hardworking, reliable and conscientious person with a diverse range of customer service experience. Good team player and able to use own initiative to achieve company objectives. Versatile and learns new tasks/skills quickly and able to work well under pressure.

EXPERIENCE

LIFEGUARD • VIRGIN ACTIVE • MAY 2021 - APRIL 2022

• Keeping the poolside clean, supervising swimmers at all times.

LUGGAGE PORTER/CONCIERGE ASSISTANT · LONDON MARRIOTT HOTEL PARK LANE · APRIL 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2020

Provide knowledge of the local area and hotel, positively engage
with guests, colleagues and our service providers, assist guests with
their luggage, assist with rooming and offer further assistance, book
tickets, tours, car service, assist with restaurant recommendations
and bookings.

NIGHT PORTER • LONDON MARRIOTT HOTEL PARK LANE • APRIL 2016 - APRIL 2017

 Answered Concierge relating emails, in charge of In Room Dining and Housekeeping at night, Delivered food and beverages, amenities.

LAUNDRY PORTER • LONDON MARRIOTT HOTEL PARK LANE • FEBRUARY 2016 - APRIL 2016

 Guest and staff laundry management, received and stored deliveries, assisted with any housekeeping request.

KITCHEN PORTER • LONDON MARRIOTT HOTEL PARK LANE • IUNE 2014 - APRIL 2015

• Kept kitchen clean and sanitized, Assisted with food preparation, washing all cooking tools.

EDUCATION

2022

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER COURSE
- IT Career Switch

2021

NPLQ (National Pool Lifeguard Qualification)

2020

HEALTH AND SAFETY AWARENESS

2019

EMERGENCY FIRST AID
AT WORK

2019

GLOBAL SECURITY TIER 1-2-3

2011

CSIK FERENC HIGH SCHOOL BUDAPEST